foxmarks.com 2010-06-24

# Foxmarks: Privacy Policy - Foxmarks Wiki

### From Foxmarks Wiki

_You can see a summary of changes since the most recent version._

Your privacy, and the privacy of all registered users of foxmarks.com, is important to us. Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy. Our policy is based on the principles of notice, choice, access and security in the collection and use of all information regarding our users and their activities at our site. 

## Contents

  * 1 Notice
    * 1.1 Types of Information Collected
    * 1.2 Use of Cookies
    * 1.3 Use of Information
    * 1.4 Disclosure of Information
  * 2 Choice
  * 3 Access
    * 3.1 Security

##  Notice 

This policy tells you, among other things, what information we gather from you how we may use or disclose that information and our efforts to protect it. Please read this policy carefully, and feel free to contact us at privacy@foxmarks.com if you have any questions regarding its contents. We may change this policy at any time to correct technical or typographical errors, to increase your rights and protections or to comply with laws. If we change this policy in a way that reduces your rights or protections or adds new types of disclosures, we will provide notification before such changes would apply to information collected from or about you. 

###  Types of Information Collected 

In connection with your use of our site, we ask for and may collect a variety of information from and about you in different ways. For example, when you register to use our site, we ask for and store your name and email address. In addition, when you use Foxmarks to synchronize your bookmarks with our server, we collect information such as the date and time of synchronization, your IP address, which version of our software you are using, and other information related to the transaction. As an intermediary in the synchronization process, we collect and store your bookmarks. We may also collect the information you disclose in any of our chat rooms, blogs, wiki pages, discussion groups, bulletin boards, and email you send to us. 

###  Use of Cookies 

Use of our site may require that you accept the use of cookies, which are small data files that our Web site sends to your browser for storage on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to protect confidential data, track activity at our site and better serve your needs and interests. 

###  Use of Information 

We use your personally identifying information to register you as a user of the site and to control access to your bookmarks. We may use your email address to contact you directly to alert of you of technical problems with your account, or, unless you opt out, to contact you regarding Foxmarks services or products. (To opt out at any time, please log into [your account](http://login.foxmarks.com/account "http://login.foxmarks.com/account").) We will never sell your email address to 3rd parties. We may also associate your personally identifying information with information we collect about your preferences and activities at the site, such as the particular pages you request at the site or other transactions you effect through the site in order to vary the content you receive in future visits to the site. 

We may analyze in aggregate the bookmarks of all users in order to deliver services of interest to other users. Such aggregate analysis will always exclude any personally identifying information. For instance, if we notice that many users are suddenly bookmarking a new site, we may display that site in a list of “hot sites.” 

###  Disclosure of Information 

We may disclose information to fulfill certain legal and regulatory requirements or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others’ rights or to prevent harm. 

##  Choice 

You may choose to delete your account at any time. Instructions on how to delete your account are available here. 

You may also choose to uninstall Foxmarks from your computer at any time. Instructions on how to uninstall Foxmarks are available here. 

##  Access 

At any time after you have created an account on our site, you may log in to your account at <http://www.foxmarks.com/> to view information about your account and make changes to such information. Once those changes are confirmed, any new item of information will replace the corresponding information previously provided. 

###  Security 

Please remember that you play a valuable part in security as well. Your password to access our site, which you select at registration, should never be shared with anyone and should be changed frequently. And, after you have finished using our site, you should log off and exit your browser so no unauthorized persons can use our site with your name and account information. Remember that any information you voluntarily disclose on-line in any news or message postings, discussion groups or chat rooms may be collected and used by others without your permission. Furthermore, if you provide any information to parties who operate Web sites that are linked to or from our site, different rules may apply to their collection, use or disclosure of your personal information. We encourage you to review these sites’ policies before revealing any sensitive or personal information. 

Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. 

This file last modified October 24, 2006.
